# Carmen Hui

huicarmen22@gmail.com |416-898-1600| Toronto, Ontario LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carmen-h-7bbb59171/ | Github: https://github.com/Karm3nz

Website: https://karmanz.github.io/Portfolio/

## CAREER SUMMARY

Front-end Web Developer with extensive experience in customer service, and education in business management from Ryerson University. Recently earned a certificate in full stack flex web development from the University of Toronto, with newly developed skills in collaboratively building applications, utilizing git branching workflow in a collaborative project, building client-side web applications, Javascript, CSS, HTML, and responsive web design. Passionate about creating life-enhancing user experiences, continuous learning of web development, and collaborating with others to develop meaningful mobile and web applications.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

 HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, GIT, Github, Bootstrap, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, Express.js, MySQL

# **PROJECTS**

#### Date-Night

- A planner application that aids users with looking for the nearest theatre, selection of movie, showtime, and saving their "date-night" plans for future viewing.
- UI Designer of a group of 5
- HTML, CSS, Materialize (CSS Framework), jQuery, Javascript, Fire Base, Gracenote API
- https://ivanduranic.github.jo/date-night-planner/ https://github.com/ivanduranic/date-night-planner

#### Weather Dashboard

- A tools and utility application that allows users to search by city to display current weather forecasts, forecasts for the next 7 days, as well as saving those searches.
- Technical Lead
- HTML, CSS, ¡Query, Javascript, Bootstrap, Moment, Open Weather API
- https://karm3nz.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/|https://github.com/Karm3nz/Weather-Dashboard

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Starbucks Canada 2015- Present

3740 Midland AveScarborough, ON MiV  $_4$ V $_3$ 

Barista

- Sequenced beverages to craft with quality and efficiency while maintaining moments of connection with customers
- Flexed to various positions on the floor to support other co-workers to meet business needs
- Suggestive sold and took beverage orders in cafe and on drive-thru to help meet daily sales targets
- Cycle-tasked maintenance of coffee brewing, replenishment of various supplies and ingredients, lobby checks, and food warming

## Allan B. Shusterman Barrister & Solicitor & Notary

2012-2018

3320 Midland Ave, Scarborough, ON M1V 5E6

Secretary

- Utilized Conveyancer Do Process software to maintain client data and creating correspondences
- Provided general price quotes to potential new clientele
- Assembled client reports relating to overall transaction of properties for lawyer's review and organized physical and electronic files for the office's filling system
- Assisted law clerk with routine tasks in will and estate dealings (faxing, certifying checks, and deposits to trust account), and maintaining receptionist duties

## **EDUCATION**

#### University of Toronto, Ontario, ON

2020 - Present

University of Toronto Coding BootCamp – Full Stack Web Development Certificate
An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications.
Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

#### Ryerson University, Ontario, ON

Graduated 2018

Business Management (BComm)- Human Resources Management

A 4-year program, starting off with an undeclared major first year and learning introductory courses to get foundational business knowledge to specialize into human resources management. Educated in organizational behaviour, industrial relations, training and development, diversity and inclusion, negotiation and conflict resolution.

#### REFERENCE

Reference available upon request.